Alex Li

Profile:

Full stack engineer/architect

I have 15+ years development experience with web/app/backend/solutions.

From small project to large one, I attended as developer, architect and PM etc and completed many projects successfully.

Last few years, i built and leaded several projects such as ERP, MES, Travel booking, delivery system and payment service etc and has good experience as remote developer with oversea team members for several years.

I'm passionate engineer, love to learn new technologies and don't afraid new challenges.

I'll try to satisfy my clients with my best and it is just my value and happiness to make client's business success.

Skills Summary:

Main focused area

- Travel Booking Service Development
- Delivery Service Development
- Payment Service Development
- ERP/MES/SCADA
- Blockchain Solution Development
- Other Web/Mobile Apps

Technical Stacks

- backend : golang/nodejs/asp.net/laravel/j2ee spring/Strapi
- front : reactjs/angular/wejs/jsp/php/wordpress
- app : iOS/android native, react-native

Others

- ibm cloud/AWS/Google cloud
- mysql/postgres/db2/mssql/oracle/mongodb
- docker/kubernates/Openshift
- Selenium/Junit/Jest
- firebase/kinvey

Qualifications:

Master's Degree of Computer Science

Languages:

Chinese, English, Korean

Education:

- 2001 2006 Beijing Information Science & Technology University, Computer Science
- 2006 2008 Beijing Information Science & Technology University, Computer Science (Master's Degree)

Employment History:

ShengTianYang, China

Web/Mobile Developer

2010-2015

- Tommy Now, Tommy Snipsnap, Roar for us, Milkcrate App development(React Native, Unity)
- Video CMS Development(AngularJS/Php)
- Cloud File Sharing Solution Development(Electron)

Neusis, USA(Remote)

Web/Mobile Developer

2016-2017

- DLP Solution Development(Windows Kernel Driver/C++)
- IPTV Service Platform Development(Java/J2EE, iOS/Android)
- ETL Solution Development(Java/SWT)
- Transport Delivery System(Angular, Nodejs)
- Skycoin Backend/Admin Panel Development(golang, angularJS)
- MES System development(golang, reactJS)

Room-Res, Australia(Remote)

S/W Architect/Engineer

2018-2020

• Hotel Booking Service Development(React JS, PHP, golang)

Greenbay, China

S/W Team Leader/Architect

2020-2021

- MES System development(golang, reactJS)
- ERP System development(ASP.NET, ReactJS)
- Scada System development(C++, Electron)
- Payment System Development(ReactJS, NodeJS, Laravel)
- · Other mobile apps